{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Wood Gutter Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","__cache./api/resource/task/40269/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40269,"taskName":"Wood Gutters - Install","taskDescription":"Install or Completely Replace Wood Gutters","xmTaskDescriptor":"Wood Gutter Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":113,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Wood vinyl rain guard cover","textMessagingName":"Inst Wood Gutter","rolloverLongDesc":"Rarely used in most locales. Sometimes wooden gutters are combined with aluminum downspouts.","rolloverShortDesc":"Wood gutters are still a favorite in some traditional homes.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Completely Replace Wood Gutters.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Wood Gutter Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Wood Rain Gutters","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":65,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Wood Gutter Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Wood Gutters - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Wood Gutter Project","urlName":"Wood-Gutters-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Wood Gutter Installation Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"Wood,vinyl,rain,guard,cover,drainspouts,copper,aluminum,Gutters","emcCategoryOid":-12038,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":573,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40269/":{"taskOID":40269,"originalTaskOID":40269,"setID":573,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5315,"questionDisplayText":"Gutter Style","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What style of gutter do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6039,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard (square edge)","answerDisplayText":"Standard (square edge)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6037,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Standard (\"Ogee\"-decorative detail)","answerDisplayText":"Standard (\"Ogee\"-decorative detail)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2905,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Half round","answerDisplayText":"Half round","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5316,"questionDisplayText":"Gutter Size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size gutter would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":480,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"4\"","answerDisplayText":"4\"","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":509,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5\" (Standard)","answerDisplayText":"5\" (Standard)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":536,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6\"","answerDisplayText":"6\"","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1059,"questionDisplayText":"Stories of Home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6339,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5315,"questionDisplayText":"Gutter Style","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What style of gutter do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6039,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard (square edge)","answerDisplayText":"Standard (square edge)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6037,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Standard (\"Ogee\"-decorative detail)","answerDisplayText":"Standard (\"Ogee\"-decorative detail)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2905,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Half round","answerDisplayText":"Half round","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6039,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard (square edge)","answerDisplayText":"Standard (square edge)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6037,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Standard (\"Ogee\"-decorative detail)","answerDisplayText":"Standard (\"Ogee\"-decorative detail)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2905,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Half round","answerDisplayText":"Half round","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5316,"questionDisplayText":"Gutter Size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size gutter would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":480,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"4\"","answerDisplayText":"4\"","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":509,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5\" (Standard)","answerDisplayText":"5\" (Standard)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":536,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6\"","answerDisplayText":"6\"","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":480,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"4\"","answerDisplayText":"4\"","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":509,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5\" (Standard)","answerDisplayText":"5\" (Standard)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":536,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6\"","answerDisplayText":"6\"","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1059,"questionDisplayText":"Stories of Home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6339,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6339,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true}